Guide to the Divinity School, Yale University, Photographs and Memorabilia
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Divinity School, Yale University, photographs and memorabilia
1889-1959
RU 772
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
(3 boxes)
The materials consist of photographs of faculty, students, and various school related events. Included is an index of students in 1942 and a group portrait of the Yale Divinity School Class of 1889.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 21 (YRG 21), Records of the Yale Divinity School.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs of faculty, students, and various school related events. Included is an index of students in 1942 and a group portrait of the Yale Divinity School Class of 1889.
Photographs; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Divinity School
- Photographs and memorabilia, Series I
  - Convocation: groups, classes, faculty, 1898, circa 1911-1938, 1957- 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Berkeley Divinity School and Center convocation, 1939 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Group photograph and identification guide, 1942-10-23 (Folder 2, Folder 1)
- Photograph of Class of 1889, Accession 2001-A-082
  - Class of 1889 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Divinity School photographic negatives, 1951-1953; Accession 19ND-A-491
  - Class of 1952
    - McAllister, James L., Jr., 1951 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mapes, Richard Walter and Mrs. Richard Walter Mapes (1953 Divinity non-graduate), 1952 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1953
    - Allen, Joseph L., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Asbury, Beverly A., 1952 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Asleson, Dix A., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Atkinson, Theodore M., Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Baldwin, Charles A., 1952 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Beam, Paul V., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Beardslee, Alvord M., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Booth, Ralph H., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Borden, James I., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Braulio, Ana Ines, 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Donald K., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Canestrari, Gene E., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Cannon, Ralph A., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chambers, James C., 1952 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chapman, Lyle S., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chappell, Willie A., Jr., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chenery, Frederick L., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Clarke, Ronald O., 1952 November 29 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dameron, Mary Anne, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Alan J., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - DuFresne, C. Richard, 1952 November 25 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Erickson, Claiborne R., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Follansbee, Mark A., Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Forsberg, C. Robert, 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Forsberg, Joan, 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Frank, William R., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Fudge, Robert A., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Goering, Paul L., 1952 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Green, Dana S., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hall, William M., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hannon, Billy Joe, 1952 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hausske, Trevor A., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hickman, Hoyt L., 1952 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Holloway, Earl M., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Howland, William C., Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Hunt, Horace H., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Jahns, Robert H., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Ralph E., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Keans, Lena A., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Kohlhofer, Leonard B., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Leidenfrost, Theodore E., 1952 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Long, Harold D., 1952 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Longley, John H., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Lovell, Robert D., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Luckey, Charles P., Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - McGill, Evelyn C., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - MacInnis, Donald E., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Magill, Samuel H., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Manice, Edward A., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Mead, Richard T., 1952 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Miho, Fumiye, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Miller, William Lee, 1953 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Moss, John A., 1952 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Murphy, DeLeon T., Jr., 1953 April (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Peebles, I. Hall, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Philpot, William M., 1952 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Poling, Charles E., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Poling, Paul David, 1952 November 20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Pry, Guy E., 1952 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Raines, Robert A., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Romanides, John S., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Russell, John A., Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Sand, Morton Y., 1953 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Sandau, Wayne R., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Schrag, Calvin O., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Scott, Allen W., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Seibert, Violette (Lindbeck, Mrs. George Arthur), Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Shafer, George W., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Skeele, Robert E., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Bardwell L., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Harry E., 1952 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Souders, Robert A., 1953 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Spilman, Kenneth E., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Starbuck, Robert B., 1952 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Strickland, John O., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Summers, Stanford G., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Tappan, Richard E., 1953 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Taylor, John H., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Underwood, Ralph L., Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Van Goor, Robert E., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Van Vactor, Lloyd, 1952 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Vieth, Richard F., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Whetstone, G. Michael, Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Woodland, J. Philip, Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Yetter, Robert N., 1953 January (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Young, Ione (Gunnarson, Mrs. John A.), 1952 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Yordon, Henry K., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Zerkel, Bernie, Jr., 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Zerkel, Betty, 1953 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Faculty
    - Hein, Norvin Jacob, 1953 May (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Lansdale, Hubert P., 1953 May (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Morris, Raymond P., Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Pope, Liston (Dean), 1953 May (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Underwood, Kenneth, 1953 May (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Young, Franklin W., Circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Composite class photograph
    - Class of 1952, Circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1953, Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)